Test 1: Default style - white text, bottom center, outline+shadow
Test 2a: \an7 top-left
Test 2b: \an8 top-center
Test 2c: \an9 top-right
Test 2d: \an4 middle-left
Test 2e: \an5 middle-center
Test 2f: \an6 middle-right
Test 2g: \an1 bottom-left
Test 2h: \an2 bottom-center
Test 2i: \an3 bottom-right
Test 3a: \pos top-center (960,100)
Test 3b: \pos mid-left (100,540)
Test 3c: \pos mid-right (1820,540)
Test 3d: \pos bottom-center (960,980)
Test 3e: \pos dead center (960,540)
Test 4a: fully opaque (\alpha00)
Test 4b: 50% transparent (\alpha80) - top
Test 4c: 75% transparent (\alphaC0) - center
Test 5a: fill 50% transparent (\1a80), outline full
Test 5b: outline 50% transparent (\3a80) - top
Test 6a: no border (\bord0)
Test 6b: thick border (\bord8) - top
Test 6c: thin border (\bord1) - center
Test 7a: 200% wide (\fscx200)
Test 7b: 50% narrow (\fscx50) - top
Test 8a: 200% tall (\fscy200)
Test 8b: 50% short (\fscy50) - top
Test 9a: no rotation (\frz0) - center
Test 9b: 15° rotation (\frz15) - top
Test 9c: -15° rotation (\frz345) - bottom
Test 10: fade in 2s, fade out 2s (\fad 2000,2000)
Test 11: WideText style (ScaleX=150 in style def)
Test 12: TallText style (ScaleY=130 in style def)
Test 13: Heavy outline (6px blue from style)
Test 14: Combined - pos+rotate+scale+fade
Test 15a: red text, bold back to white
Test 15b: italic text normal text - top
Test 16a: \an7 + \pos(100,100) top-left anchor
Test 16b: \an5 + \pos(960,540) center anchor
Test 17a: bottom-center (simultaneous)
Test 17b: sign at top (simultaneous)
Test 17c: middle-left (simultaneous)